it's hard to actually see command-line
calculate introduce one history is
requesting
and also
replace
this were here
wise and packed like ashley except
actresses all one were sold one word
they're pretty files there that people
are come down
and fell into the computers
that's yours uh... secure research tools
house
usually anything more password
throughout the semester insisted again
even more confusing
number one january electric a point
where if i don't do it quickly trouble
world
he
we assume you have no computer
background
stanley kubrick
one
with eastward but yet
went
atkinson
here
i think
we're gonna get toward front
there's too much for things going on
here one if you want to be able to work
as you go
if you've gives the media
you have to build something up as you go
anti-competitive bilateral everytime
mechanical compete because
one of the senate is taking steps to get
where you are
and you don't know that lots that
consumer market time
he might be such that he can't get
parkway and and work with that paper
here
trial for things
and doing it just from a final gets
difficult
in the end of the one that book
lab file relenting from
more likely many many files yeah and
then you're awesome i have to command
line
and calvert protector
word system if the flow yet
and it's not because if i prefer all of
you have wanted u_s_-canada wide here
so you were doing a lot of stuff about
the big picture rectangular frustrating
yeah that's right now
that
with a plague on an open still
upset also cite that him and into the
aristide channels
if you want to copy and paste it from
the irish channel
and it is
also writing in today's notes
on the class website
which i've made a nice little for link
for them
you all can you please are u r l dot com
slash research tools kicked out of
eleven water
jump there about having test
no i spell my last name
it'll be a lecture sects forty thousand
one thing
or nine
say they have a lot getting these to
install
we have a success
it's going to say lots and lots of stuff
back to you
work pretty well
you misspelled research
uh... or scheme of things for
the uh... extra vmware
oxford
and that's gonna ask you yes or no to
continue
this is going to test your typing
accuracy
so you gotta learn to read it if you do
it sometimes has been spaces and
sometimes there's not been spaces are
dashes
it'll take awhile
always figured out that i have to get
this is one word there's no spaces in
there
even that should be crashing l there's
no spaces
thinking up
here there's no spaces in here
it doesn't matter where you are
when your phone software is going into
the system of the horn virtual machine
so it doesn't
you can always go back your home
directory by just typing stevie
had
you can see if you could also be cd
and i was in the same time
goal
i was getting lazy
sometimes they'll fight with each other
one thing was to set up its world out
there that once called him i can't
compete but
it's uncommon
we need to install some software
for costly into big
if we all try to do it in the most
popular misleading
i know it's extras
in english pretty sleep like one extra
stuff
there's extra stuff that you need for
some of our tools to run correctly today
door installed the pacing guides
and we also need a place to go with it
expired
we're gonna make the caveat
and technical who was going to make
p_b_s_ force in the background
they're not going to use it by hand
but if it's not bear ups like
haha this to be the comment about the
spaces verses not business
so our desired legislative rainfall
incidentally disappear
surgery rolls one wife's that there's no
spaces in there
and so you can do you know if someone
wants to replace those commands back
into the topic everybody was laws in the
chat session
and that will be al
proposal
your run
all of these and therefore more nato you
could also combine though boxing
yet
fewer doesn't matter
progressing here hasn't thought software
so if you need something you look at it
yet
corrections as on the virtual machine
uh... right
yes
virtual she was on my computer three
three three cathy asked uh...
the main system worked
leah
the files are memory's not being uh...
ram
acts like it
yesterday you talked earlier for your
review can stick the three on the stand
wind together
this is the explicit way to work on
attractive gets here
time now to remember the password t
so i do this in a separate for from
working
farm back where you guys when i went
through preparing for class
you're all again
so that you see the same thing that idea
the catch up here
secured
statements
this is the nice thing about
clinics especially given to you is that
all the stuff has prevailed
you're not running on the internet
trying to find random files
and i can sometimes lead to you
installing things that are bad
their combined the two together
at that point road that leads to find
one
using
there was a lexus is abortion or several
different versions of one x tools for
installing quite frequently
we can say aps
search
and then we can say like paypal
after church for things that are part
this is doctor isn't so installed
just two days
because the pipeline
tried the debussy twenty year class time
there's twenty three
hundred
icon packages v stall
thursday time of software none of which
cost anything to install
lots
you'll see there's all kinds of fun
things in here
sub which makes sense that other stuff
my nominee
and might start to talk about a minute
forty five seconds that word
will go ahead
the first action we didn't do anything
about this is their stuff going on the
background it doesn't matter
first they can still
go ahead and start with a lecture as
long as we did he consult something else
going to be installing in one window
can't run around and a consulting firm
five different windows
you know pay-per-view inflated take a
hike
but we're short off with
ke pass accesses our password managing
to llc
that's going to keep track of our
password fits and keep them in the
cricket file
if you have any dropbox before this is a
service where
the cloud keeps a copy of your files
they can synchronize between any
computer where you have dropbox
installed on it
as great except for this and security
worries about those wiki pass acts it's
not a problem because we're going to put
in cricket file on onto our dropbox
so we're going to go ahead and set up
ke pass exports this is a tool that you
can use on
mcevoy next windows offered platforms
it's missing
eyeballs are parents
and
toriente or devices
so if you've got those
you may have to fire service if you
really want to have your keep
ke pass
file
with you at all times
on your phone
that you have to look at something like
one password actually cost
hopefully someday in near future
keep aspects will end up on phones
soaring to go ahead and add to this
virtual machine
over the top
an alias wounded since pass on the
bright click
on this top bar
doing ads appear like we did with our
team acts in our terminal osce on
and go back to this
application launcher
and pressed forward
before forget today will has set up of
the new camera
pointing at me in this
so we'll see about video actually works
out spots
but we're going attorneys accessories
and you'll see this thing looks like a
key and much of that
it's sticky
we're that cross on it
so it's like
keypads express
and at the top
you're gonna see if he backs expert here
yes i think i have to admit it so i have
a note files got everything that i a
controversial machine so that
if you are pure without the first
machine but just what the notes
he should be able to accompany
reproduced everything i've done
the goal is that there's nothing here
that's
special and you can't take away with you
so inside it dot
go ahead and get that button weichert
make my whenever you're
and start out in contacts
and you should see a menu like that
for crack will interface
this tool
right now it's not going to any file so
we need to open up a new database
third open for existing stock new four
we want to create one
now here
you're going to watch me do summer show
you passwords so i'm not gonna do
anything fancy but for u need to take a
good password
remember that after a few forget this
aspirin
all rather packwood's go away
so basically means
inoculated dispatch
the n_s_a_ paul but
enough for us
pick a password i'm going to pick them
up
that's not a good passwords
this way i cannot remember at the top
what paul as though i don't forget gonna
pick a password that's pretty good
and memorable
o'clock numbers letters
means the punctuation in it
you'd
haven't recognized patterns for sure you
can
if nothing else you can open up a new
finally populated enters into it
so i doubt that demo
type it again
argument hope demo
if you can it be accurate password that
you're going to keep
if you need a stick and no had put in
your wallet and and
walk in the state somewhere else
that's okay
but don't show it to your neighbor
absolutely not near secom passport it
should not be your wiki password
it shouldn't be your government aspirin
usually sorghum agency
it should be something that you cannot
use anywhere else
after recycling is a very bad
i know they see easier but there still
is here
so that you have to remember one
password not to make a good password
the world but people often use the tools
that at least six months
i've had to change
harder password at least six months in
jail
that's just a lot of work and forget
washington times
you'll remember one one password in the
school takes care of everything else for
threw it away
tape before you anything
so that we don't usually hear
work typically do
is i would call mine
by mining
just in case this file gets dissociated
from yourself it's always been a big
profits of ends up on someone else's
here is not the end of the world
but i would pick your name so it's a
hobbyist
new and other people when they try to
open it
also use you they might want a patchwork
it's a and we've now got ourselves a
place to put all bar
as past ones that were going to be
creating and that we create in the past
so thought i had a great one response
because we're all going to have the same
password for the research tools account
and wanna hang on behalf
does save
under file
and then just pick your name
enable saving in your home directory
onto that's a that's here just to show
back for that was
ekkada this direct real estate here
you can always get it from
browse other folders water of it
turns over and youthforseva hands
and what they've research tools at your
home directory for this account
and once we get drop box set up we're
going to do this file into dropbox
you can use for multiple machines and
not just having a virtual machine them
frustrating
finality books
is to save the file so we can say
stated a along with the state at the
table i think it
appear worth his name
if you your name
tip if you don't hear about it on a
interactions initiatives
church where he
says the girl in critical care
whenever we say that we're not gonna
worry that are
after they've been given away the bad
guys
we're going to go up to you
groups
and add new group
and when it comes to groups it's up to
you how do you want to
to put them together
lead you into one group
because we'll have a lot of password
relate this to come brusett added group
and the group's going to be ccom
if you'd like you can pick a funny icon
motions i found him very well for me
this is like a heart with three
different color
tonight quick update
and now you have a seat on folder
you have any mailfolder came with the f_
overcame my
with nothing in any of it
so select this account holder
sloops and if you put something in our
own folder don't worry bout it's easiest
for things
and around
if your favourite conover to sleep with
a false
but screen entry
agnew entry under entries
anneke circuit is a lot there are nice
shortcuts to this seeking
as you go through and have a lot of
accounts
consolidate things to add new entry
it's going to give you this nice display
of evidence here and we'll go back will
go through twice once for the research
tools one with the symbol on the more
poor people live in its features
for applied all
think about
what you might search on the research
tools
he felt that eleven
virtual machine islamic way
because i might search for virtual
machine might search through research
tools
i like search for two thousand eleven
you want to make it easy on yourself
he'd go to the username send the town
anti-police search
tools
exactly as you would type it into the
consul
you wrote that's where i ca website like
yahoo dot com mcdougal dot com or
something like that
then you would put your own for him we
don't have one
in this case
when we've had a passport it's gonna
hide it for us
that's nice
in a room like this if you'd like to get
a secure password you don't want it up
on but for me i don't line up on the
screen seven to see it
i'm a change that dale and it's going to
go ahead with yourself because i have
all here quickly eyeballs
then you can see what your typing if
you're by yourself on a lot topper
computers
where you know people are starting over
your shoulder
you can go ahead with that plan
and our password
means an exclamation point
party
two thousand eleven
he defected again to make sure they
don't screw it up
and here you can type whatever comments
you felt like
so they could say you bring to you
one x story eleven point zero four
the f_b_i_
eight nine five dash three c_-one
elective course number or whatever you
might start on
if this pattern is going to expire and
you know if this works and how you could
set that up here
and up liberated okay and save our first
password there
missile database
them ahead ok
so it's a we want to create
a new account coming in the past words
will go ahead and create something
thirty-three baden's up here which are
also the equivalent of
the menus
some of what's wrong with the little
green heroin a wrenches add new entry
the same is doing
entries pageantry
who put back
florida coast onepass
messing around
your name
boring
and we need to take approx worked at the
point where the program can really help
you
with her on the eyeball for making easy
were in fact
is jen
but many russians generate
thirds generated password
and this gives you a tool that will help
you build a password
and you to give it some parameters and
then
hit the button generate against that
create password saddam his again on
arrival
make sure that eyeball
have bluelist
if a company that that's great out
politically
pecans what's going to be in the
password who's back we're going to be
unreadable
sore at all our properties letters
lower case letters and numbers
white faces the minus line
the underlying special characters
it's often wife to click the exclude
look-alike characters that's the one in
the al
andy alwyn zero
we can be painful
a good thing to do is also insure the
proper contains characters from every
group
check back to check everything possible
here
we said we want to properly twenty five
characters long
it's telling us this is a hundred and
fifty three day pass word which is
begin
ever hit the jackpot
and there is are very ugly password
i'd like to all memorize that and i
would have to be in the day
is the kind of passport you can use that
super secure
but will try to you
if you have to take this
especially our phone or like a tablet
where you don't have for keyboard
it's kind of stuff
so let me show you what you might do
typically specially for password you're
going to have to use elsewhere
if you do you know the pattern you
wanted to type it in
there's also pronounce opening recon
over here
and you can get to generate
and it will generate something that
tries to be
purnell civil
did know that your
fades
question buck
network
that's no fun
where typically deal for for sites that
they need to be able to type that's a
into an iphone ipod or andrew tablet
they'll pick something more mental size
like fifteen still pretty good
alter not a special characters the white
spaces the miners underlined
and the uppercase letters
it's hard to do you prefer case letters
a tablet you have to hit
shift button and it goes away after
every character
so this way
you'll have
depart turnoff political like characters
okay
here for you to generate
here we have
reacts asked to would be
l nine counting
not terrible
you can live without password and might
actually be able memorize it after a
couple months leaving at all times
but this is not about past if you have
to put this on the computer screen and
then type into a phone not terrible
you know carry
your passwords now in there
and now have a passport that's not too
bad
very secure
you can probably survive typing since we
had uh...
pet ok
and we now have a whole test
account
and if we have a turnover is going to go
ahead and plate
if you go up to that account so we
select test
so highlight on their menu taps
if you're a quick comments
you're going to get a couple of
different options
if you notice the username is got starts
her in the background menu in the packet
that starts going through it
there's two cases where
this may help you one is it for a room
like this if i showed my actual ke pass
x-files
which i can actually do for you
former dragon mikey pacify was with real
passwords
over new screens you can see it
you can see
you might need you account but he was on
my apple that bucket
delicious
bugle etcetera etcetera
you can tell my username or my password
from the file so if you see it over my
shoulder i'm not worried about getting
my password
which you can do is there is a copy
username to put toward
and if we go over to his terminal
edit paste just to see it
there's a username
everything is passed
and if we go back here
right click again
copy the pact word
you could go over to a website and
pasting that password
there's the proper dictation and where
you can if you're in an actual website
that would not show up
so that way
if someone's looking over your shoulder
you can log into a web site and nobody
has seen your passport will probably see
your username websites reasoning but
at least the password is being protected
don't forget after each change this
thing does not although saved
so file
state database
after everything to make
highly recommend you save it for the
white you may have updated website and
lost that password
well for the path to recovery system in
so now we have a proper containers such
this is a very flat so you have to
create accounts
even expect u
show and pretty municipalities that half
of generator
and create some passport that without
actually you don't have a drop off the
captain attraction you're gonna put that
in here
dot file
we're done
to be able to flushes drop off astronaut
here freezing dropbox and ke pass x
you probably need to keep it safe
someplace offsite
master password for
he backtracked
and a drop-off password because if your
walk up to a new machine
carter computers haven't stolen
people to get that password back
for drop box did you keep that x file
and then you have to have the master
password
to steely dan on sixteen th password
now this has got
versions for the mac
for windows and one x
so if you go back to your office you can
download
onto your windows machine if you cut
whatever operating system
you can download ke pass acting you can
use the same file on it
that way you can work between the scenes
any dispute barker passwords
like me you might have fifty under
passwords for websites for the
university i have
hander fifteen passwords for all that
crazy computers
have a different after pretty calm that
i have dropped four blackboard
all us that goes in here and then
you can get your brain throw it away
next topic is going to be
dropbox
sure
this is the one thing that if you pick
up anything i posses nothing else
he passed that's
i'd only found out about this about six
months ago
but actually passed
then no with u
so we have one of our righty admins
actually has his
passport file in dropbox
andy's that and the security folks took
a look at it and give my thumbs up
so that made it past
the folks from
d_c_
in the government you off
because it's pretty good way to go
and it's free
if you'd want password i think it's
expensive fast
at the drop box
because of the drop box
is that you've got files all over the
place
he parties he and his clocks
you're not your normal work computer
we've got you on classroom computers
that you want your files but few you
need to be able to share stuff around
these people follow you
so there's lots of services out there
that use the cloud that basically have a
home store somewhere out there
probably in the middle of the desert
some places with armed guards around
somewhere building
and there's a great computer you log in
the service in a more than update the
files aren't active here
so if you write a word document for your
class
you then go over to allow computer
decided that you want that word
automatically appear on the computer
there
if they actually had multiple filesystem
you could use that
if you're switching between periods
while the current organizations
face which from the east coast to west
coast from when you were to the
university
those files wouldn't than falling
figure with dropbox
as a whole bunch of other services
with his father for that and we get a
free account
uh... few gigabyte soonest
singer or educational users if you use
your
u_n_ eighteen militarized or anything
that's dot you a show you some of you
have a seat on the email address
then you'll get some extra space and if
you were for people you get an extra
five hundred megabytes
still end up with that basically people
over two and a half gigabyte flashdrive
he can run around with
but still have to carry anything
their one really big drawback conditions
of security and that's if you go on the
ship
they don't have internet
i thought there
the nice thing though is if you have a
cult operetta right you can
synced up on a computer does have a
pulled out on the as a wall
becomes ship with you in you'll have at
least
a snapshot of when you left
if someone steals your computer
and your
ke pass x_ files on there and you're
critical presentation for class next
week is on there
you can embark appear when someone gets
back to work
that's really nice to have service like
this
if your headed dropbox account that's
great we're gonna go ahead and install
the software for dropbox
and then if you don't have an account
create one
and i just want to warn you i may give
you a link
that's my referral
when it gets kind of weird act
go straight up at the time i get a
little extricate backup file space for
if you guys type using that link
so if you think that's not okay um...
doing questions will hold a hopeless
feel free to use your growing from
somewhere else in the class or if you
have one in your email from somebody
else use that
and once you get it out
you can refer friends and family
and co-workers
but the united states not appreciate
for case please join the service and i
get a bonus
it's one of these obscene pyramid
schemes
people are fairly happy a ticketing
stand for everybody asking
for coral
pledge or clocks there's lots of them
drop boxes
probably the most popular and common one
it gives the chief rejects
you it will give you
as a part of being a student i don't get
this fellow students catid
the wildcat email now comes with a
microsoft skydrive
with twenty five people bites which is
nice
that doesn't work on one xa doesn't work
on the mac except for through our web
browser
you have a twenty five to drive it
actually paid for by being here
uh... your tuition how about page
coverage dot
but we can't use it in front of one x so
we haven't used this factor
a drive over yes to a direct service
there's many services
and
yes there's many services and in fact
in the notes there's no way to wikipedia
page with about five hundred services in
it
a lot of them don't wear on
on one x
an alarm that were on the mac
and try to be something that works
everywhere
is free and that would give you some
resource base two gigabytes of actually
get a pretty good for this class
most of our files are going to be taxed
in very small
if you have a letter to you if you can
use that
for other things but for this class
i'm only gonna show you how to use
dropbox
dropbox you can use it your web browser
you can also install software doesn't
automatically
so we're going to be automatic version
so if you haven't
create an account andropov sorry
brings over here in chile
this u r l
so if you type in
this link right there
this is the one where i get extra space
feels guilty
you can do this on the virtual machine
or you can do it and when did it doesn't
matter just in a web browser
greatest ex-wife he sees the um... i
received channel
so it published by click on this is not
going to look
like you'll see fit
still secret accounts
you put in your first and last name
you don't have to use
u_n_h_c_r_ draft but i don't recommend
it
because if you
afterwards go after class
go to the extent of the debbie dot
dropbox dot com slash eview
you can see that you actually get
jerzy a special deal for being a student
they always want to get you more hopeful
messed up so well that place so you are
gigabytes
for a lot more
for the district attorney if you have
done it by adding on more space
getting other people on it
schedule at work
that's connected
app
it's up to you if you are hope your
parents or not
to go ahead and create a dropbox account
as you're going a password used that
keep aspects
storing your password
i'm gonna go ahead and log in the
morning
so here's what i want a seat in dropbox
gotten
yes fickle appear my last name at the
combine u
so you're you're in the install
yall go were true that forever preparing
to do it wants to make sure you don't
click on the sixty four-bit one
bubbles will keep you all that
i don't know if you are pretty bitter
sixty four that you have to figure out
cities and you're going to want dot com
your the figure to prepare
member cannot disappear
now appear on near winnipeg here here at
seekonk you may be able to install as a
user were constructing territory
about how to manage
d_c_ com computers because we don't want
to put dropbox on
every computer by default because what
happens then is everybody who walks in
any cat what they have drop-off in op
will get
the dropbox login question
where do we are going to push you guys
command line as much as possible
so you you'll see step in the queue
retirement rent which you back toward
back manoranjan
to be thinking about the command line
times
sees the windows web browser and then
you're body
operate like it
yet you can also copy and paste from
that
suspects file got your password
so no worries saw inside of the virtual
machine
and then you can use it on windows from
the web browser
and we're working on how to handle patsy
com
so that you can actually now that s
fellowship recapping the day's top and
we'll go ahead and stall with tools
inside of one x
now this is not open-source software
so they can't put the software in it
the even q packaging system
we have to download the file for
otherwise it's not
who have like it to be
but if you go to class notes
preview going here
amenities this into the aristide chat
and this is debbie get commanders
connect
do exactly what's on their install page
so in here
you correct either way
it's whichever you prefer doing
copy and paste should go across the
virtual machine and windows
the command i'm about to trailer on
front page of the aristide
and foreign experts are switching
effect of maternal and i
says the commitment to give a shock to
see what happens
now after the election anyone believe it
all
as its not my wife
control
in that window
little white everything's on that
terminal
but go back to my
virtual machine and i mean here
i don't like what i've got it control
you
that the leaves from the curse of the
front
and then
there hadn't paid back and then back in
with the quotes review enter
runoff and grab that file
rego back
and the web browser
and didn't on cam on ways but i think
about having both
as that
we can always fall back
will jump here
copy back
links in the aristide
you know if we
because of their
vertigo didn't download this so
sixty-four x_-eighty six sixty four
means is the sixty four-bit version of
our current system running the free to
do it for him
an asterisk x eighty-six masters type of
professor we have
break like that
save link as
miss lewis show you where you're going
to
surrender i want to put you down what i
would put it in your research tools
writing their home directory
i'm doing is inside of the virtual
machine
the questionnaire you've been watching
for back and forth that was
yet uh... firefox icon to beat the pop
up there
the pace that your own
were on the page
dropbox
and you can right click on that point
appear at the top
then on here you'll right-click
save link as
downloads
it's ok but i would suggest putting on
research tools your home directory there
let's say it
already have one from a replacement
shouldn't have one
now if we go
if you're on the page without
all the files
there's nothing but the bottom line
you've chosen by selecting on their
places
that they're going downstairs research
tools at your home directory
prime minister you have a quick tricks
but it's worth knowing
so if you look here we have this
nautilus dropbox
some numbers dot then
when the command andy five some
and then novelist drop-off test
if your chapter member fortresses it
runs in our program on the file
second he said number they're not just
the data in there
it's very rare for this number match-up
aunty files
so if you see a number of certain sixty
four
tenzin twenty-one
your knowledge dropbox file that means
you have the right file
foods and the five cell
and if i was sometimes around but on
this one is and the five summary here
this is the command iran
it's returning a big number
and this number
we're going to use this number
a whole bunch later on in the semester
that checks on out to be in the file
with a vigorous different
and control c
unity of the following so control c
so and if i have some phase
and then this and they use talent
answering service in
home for their
with two home folders kid
and by the end the semester
you won't be in the area
by the using all command-line all time
type and defiance on
d five
and a new
and prospects have u
this is one
one button
if i write abt
failing to protect just typed out
off after
and you should see something that looks
like
person sixty four
and here in indy five someone
it looks like
exam unfortunately
silvery download the file so go back to
a page firebox insider
easy we ate population in the wake of
that classmates
yes the confidently
to oversee the virtual machine
open firefox has opened up a profitable
are far preferable
hastened so highlight the whole upheld
shannon's advantages press the free
downloads who happens
barrio it's it's a right click that one
save link as
now click the down button here
and research tools in your home or at
least let's say
nelson from
so go back to the terminal
doing a lot of space national tiara
oh you're near symbols do collect
terminal
to see how you're in told the slashes
animals tell me where you are
type cd
presenter altogether home directory
doing a lot of specialty on again
casey had all files actually figure
now run confine park
twenty five cell
expanding ten
axle penner
so now if i mentioned i will write file
for you guys we can install it
in this commander here in the notes
theater review package dash ally
this is a way to install the actual
or of files are in the government has a
software package
when we do have to get
this is happening behind the scenes
we don't really need to understand what
this is
made by the end semester he'll have a
good deal for this if you don't it's
okay
as when you see it
done once there's instructions elsewhere
will go back
into here
and if you take that
uh... put this in the aristide to know
so you're gonna run sudo the package
that i mean things fall
and then our dropbox
debian package
if you're already there hit enter
soon after your research tools password
and it should go crazy
you all kinds of stuff
gotta pop out this window
about restoring our list
and i have explained very much about the
graphical interface that comes with the
winfield
also plays this week if you take that
the stuff that runs around here
is no saw all these little buttons and
whatnot and novelist is that file
browser some of your back she brought up
uh...
from a crack workstation four is very
much like windows explorer
that's called novelists on the system
there were a few novelists that's what
it means windows explorer
go ahead and give restart wants
i believed it leaves you with the same
kind of weird
every story is still there
thanks
which means you are about to sit next
dropbox for required
so if you look up before reported
start look at the top plate
and there it is a light comes in here
we should see anyone appear here for
dropbox
so press start dropbox
whatever kind of thing
in a few seconds drop-off of the going
if you do this little window of
progression along
it fell on the actual permanent dropbox
i really have the dropbox account
super tuesday let me know type in your
name and password
actually held by the applause passwords
becky pass x does
and i'm gonna break here bring over my
actual keep assets and show you guys
here
there's a search window up top
and the brightest rape
dropbox and hit enter
it on the search for the all the folders
and here i have a group called biosphere
and
and dropbox
and i can go on this
right-click
copy the password to put forward
i'm doing is all part of the which me
but i'm very conference program not
dumping my passport right little screen
exhausted
growers the virtual machine
for doing here
and i paste
verify password right in front of you
and nobody has seen my password
there's a scale of the bottom
computer name
when your login to drop box
down the road
if you say leave
you in ages and some were also need to
get a chance to create the gas in the
authorized things
you don't know if i want to have
i_d_ teens who are down sharply maybe
even selling your computer off to the
world
where authorization to use that computer
for your drop box files
they're hoping we can go in on the way i
think the authorized a computer and it
will never be able to update you get
your files
pick something that means something to
you here for me
i was playing with you go into
overkill machine on my desktop and i've
got one of my laptop so here i think
that laptop
tibidow affecting if you sit next you're
okay
part one of its good choice
disapprove one forty two
so may hit next
and return train say something
so you don't want to fight
what i think his laptop is what i picked
to go and pick something else like
classroom
easily be given a name if your choice
a meeting
match attractions for industry
if you've got a point where it's trying
to sell you more stuff
click normal but two fifty gigabyte one
and if you get back the next one is
typical verses
advance fee was typical
you guys are destined for granted
but the forgot password and you're gonna
have to work on this and try to catch up
so you have to figure out what password
you new password reset
state specialty or
we're getting along with steamers word
and
cease you no doubt that melody that
check up there with the indy five sound
so tight and defiant
as you m
space
any
press tab
and press enter
and now you're going to install that
and that's that wins the package he p
teaching
space
fashion
anymore
right
now if you also need to have seen loan
for which i forgot
teaching prestige for any
wasn't thinking
toolkit for any
type as you
to get permission in town
to be doing that
now procedure
at the new research tools password
okay tonight you back into this whole
process
it's gonna pop up that many of them
walking through
and so
for quick if you can
and if we had changed by screensavers
time so it's tough being walked out
workarounds
this is where they try to sell used up
pleased spend ten dollars a month or
twenty dollars a month with us and say
no or stick with the pbx
the typical
i don't want to convince the day
welcomed dropbox skip the tour
youthful if you like it
and it wants
the admin password bhavin batteries or
reversal password
if you're in the middle of that
they can be
challenging
yet we're universal machine you know
it's actually nights than that
if you know the machine you can see the
password
you can if you know it's gonna be asking
for a password in the middle of the
ballot box inactive year of the computer
back as winners would love to do
then you can copy paper had time to have
it ready to go
and so you can see him i drop box here
i was lazy only for the first name
here's my keith vaz x-files
and i have a a from opal machines
it keeps track of actors actually open
on my desktop forgetting that it does
qualify for up to close it
and that knows its heading up there so
it's got a lot filing it won't through
my files but to be planning at the same
time
behind closed up
now if you look at pier and dropbox
i have a lot of junk in mind
there's a little arrow spinning around
in circles looking back you probably
can't see this
that's it synchronizing files between
this computer and everything else that i
have
so as you've used up to a lot and i
think that changes and push them between
all of your computers
and my case
i work on about fifty computers
depending on
beforehand doing
so having this kind of thing is super
important because i've got computers in
the west coast in the east coast
so here is that you learned something
files
just got pushed around
there's audio files and powerpoints and
you can see my brown bag park
philosophy
and if you'd make this point
you know how dropbox and could you tell
us filled with flash
corrupt box
you will see
your drop box data
and i think if you have a smartphone if
you're lucky if i have one of those
you can get a lap location honest work
phone and you can go see these files
so my grocery list isn't
i pack up on the computer with any
defined at the grocery store and i
forget
what are you getting a baking section
trio bentsen there
developed a little application to
election added those files from the
policy so you can write your thesis from
the phone
and people that off
popeater
all right what's going on
the latest traveled out to you
youth
let's take a look at so i don't see an
icon
this is played
so there's no icon appear saying uh...
partly
tech history seems to be doing
in and see
is comming here
heitzmann
uh...
reruns commands are going to back up to
you
insisting upon when it is the supplier
units you you restart
the next
star dropbox i bet you do that
harry having accounts
next
and then suddenly here
and should be good
and we are running out of time
i think you can get here all day long
and we'd all pass out
what we're going to the next
is dig into you max and
creating
portlet files these are
a whole outlining slash life planning
slash controlled the world
applications
brazen
for all of that
please adjust for not to keep notes
you'll be able to put source code bits
and greater homework that in workload
infinite
goes further
class assignments
almost a point where you guys are ready
to have some small farmers i really
wanted
throw you the walls of the command lines
without
a few days of looking at things
on tuesday i'll give you guys are small
homework assignments issued
if it goes well take lots of about
twenty to thirty minutes at the very
i'll make sure to be around before class
when it is so you guys can
can sit down with me
and coterie
dropbox cure for aids
if you work in a virtual machine you
want to see her files
actively working on stuff
if you were coming in the drop box area
and you go home
they're still there still be in drop box
and you can get to them for the web
interface
so now in yorba dropbox accounts
those by over bill right here
so if you want to get them later
secured the python script that i was
working on
depict some program apple mac
there is the script that i kept around
so if you're working on something
dropbox i agree with this kind of here
really a true backup solution
it doesn't keep revision history is very
well
when it is very handy
so we'll just have this around for the
rest of class
and if we can figure out your right will
have it on the windows machines team so
that
you can
bases have files appear on both sides of
the windows and one x i do not worry
about it
or if you go back to the computer which
machines in here those files were
falling between computers eisenstein
if interpreting computers
that virtual machine have set up on this
computer is the one that knows about
your drop box if you guys are switching
seats
you're gonna have to go through all of
the gang
and you know i think that
stick to same lot all best operate out
if we have a despot divya go back to
humans
amount rebuilding virtual machine in the
next week that's got to stop in a except
for war your passport
i don't ever want to know your cockles
and if anybody ever asking for tackling
look elsewhere
youthful cake
cucusoft and church the public
we're going to get back
with a deadly now it's all part of this
from within to tell mark here on the
university
and you all have serious units accounts
that are attached for your point for
flash
webmail account
and you can share files with that to you
and what what it means more about
through right away next time we're gonna
jump brady max
and editing
whatever hair down to reassert using a
couple other philly to really start
working with writing scripts and
actually doing stuff with code
there's a lot of setup
but the pain is worth it
short-term pain long-term right
caveat property
before you were an opera click
if you take your properties i forgot
that
um... erecting virtual machine here
if you saved it
travis church where ducky
a_t_v_
if you see a walk next to it means you
go back here
here and you file
state database
and file quit
clothes ironed out
m_v_
k_g_b_ file
cubicles flash
dropbox
and that will move uart
he did have a singer dropbox folder
till then want to make sure that
if you look at his ability are spinning
around word saw that
things happen
you're gonna see your t_v_ file in the
list of recently changed files
anderson close attention to be doing
that proper record weighing no your drop
box password
actually very drop-off accurately
minor detail
right
yeah so you you'd before you walk out of
here
part a piece of paper anna repair
dropbox after donna and take that with
you for sure or you're not going to get
into a player
if you are double check
you could go back to the website
for dropbox and you can by hit refresh
up here
all right there is
for the open l c
your file appear in their so i've got
mine
side now seems like demo password
through sms there
youth
the keypad
does not have a website associated with
it
so that is just a file that's up to you
keep track of
so that's why we have your drop box
aspirin and keep aspects
password
yet that's ok
so what i didn't
desire and this can enter my homework
three
if you want to see
your file name if you remember the name
of your file
you can do
if you run penelas specialty are with
pale
so give it a lot handles frequently
upriver files
we'll still have a
apartment when we got something like
this
i thought a_t_v_
and then your aunt
a move with your cv file name
and told the slash dropbox
because you might lose it and it might
be in the process of
you're halfway through something
expose previously done with it
and then sexually and if you look up out
on the screen there
till the flash dropbox
as could drop offs okay uh... files i
would take a look on the website make
sure that your t_v_ is on the website
big lesson for everyone
any x_-files never put a face
these characters are trouble
in filings
uart you could do it
an all time we showed him how to do it
whatever you have a space you're gonna
call your wife to be difficult forever
after
fall into the faces are really